Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Oh, we've been at
this all day, buddy, I get it.
Those other spots
didn't float your boat,
but wait until you see
this next place.
It screams mouse house.
Wait, can I say that?
Is that copyrighted?
Heh. There we go.
Whoop. Sorry about this,
the elevator's, uh,
being repaired.
Boom!
I just had a vision!
You're chillin'
in your new crib,
but then
you get claustrophobic,
and then you get dizzy,
and to save you...
Ta-da!
Look at that view!
Resplendent, ain't it, huh?
It's got everything.
Built-in stereo,
but be careful, those seats
are very flammable.
I'm kidding.
I'm not kidding.
Jerry, baby,
I know it's no beauty,
but let's be honest here,
with your budget,
this is all you can...
Hey! You don't just Batman me.
You haven't even seen
the trunk yet.
Ahhh!
Look, Dad. That blind cat's
playing piano.
There's a lot of weird stuff
in this city.
You just gotta keep walking.
I mean,
he's amazing on the piano,
and blind, too!
That's one cool cat.
Man,
that cat is out of sight!
This is so cool.
Whoa!
Oh, wow! Isn't he cute?
I thought I'd seen it all with
the blind, piano-playing cat.
Oh, man.
He can see!
He's a fraud!
He's a regular cat
playing the piano.
Man, I want my money back!
Ahhh.
Hey. Are you okay?
You gotta be careful next time.
You could have really hurt me.
Oh, my gosh.
Suspended? Why?
For starters,
the 100 pounds of underwear
strewn up 5th Avenue.
Oh, come on,
you can't blame me for that.
That was
a cat-and-mouse situation,
and everyone knows
you just don't get involved.
You can reapply in four weeks.
No. Please, sir,
please, just...
You... You...
You can't do that to me.
Oh.
Last week, I helped a man
do a pull-up for an hour.
An hour! He achieved
his fitness goals with me.
Okay.
What if I just...
I come and be your assistant?
Ms. Forester,
you started two months ago.
It just doesn't work like that.
Maybe this job
never was for me.
- Maybe it's not.
- You know what? I quit.
HORSE: Mm-hmm. Uh-huh.
Whoa!
- Hello.
- Hey.
Back for another free meal?
So, you new in town?
Somewhat.
You know what they say,
it's not a trip
to the Big Apple
without a walking tour
of the city.
Have you ever done one?
They're very well-reviewed,
actually, mine are.
It's a great deal, great offer.
I'm not a guest.
Then, pray tell,
why do you have a suitcase?
I'm here to interview for one
of the temporary positions.
Because of the wedding.
What wedding?
Preeta and Ben.
Ah. As in, like,
the Preeta and Ben?
New York society's
favorite couple.
It's going to be
quite the event.
Huh.
The hotel is hiring?
Yes, but they're
very exclusive.
They certainly wouldn't
hire you.
Mm.
And what did you say
your name was again?
Linda Perrybottom.
Linda Perrybottom,
unfortunately,
you just failed the test.
What?
Your interview
started the minute
that you walked in the door.
I didn't realize, I just...
Employees
of the Royal Gate Hotel
must be accommodating,
masterly,
but above all, Linda,
discreet.
If they're telling
a perfect stranger
the intimate details
of the inner workings of
this hotel's private events,
well, that doesn't
quite cut it now, does it?
- I'd...
- May I see your resume?
- Please?
- Uh...
Yes, of course.
Thank you.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, you've had
a lot of really cool jobs.
Yes, I have.
- The Dorsey?
- Dorsey.
The Armada.
These all are hotels?
Well, none are in New York.
I just moved here from London.
Listen, Linda.
I don't think you're right
for this weekend.
Oh.
We just need someone more...
local.
Well, I understand.
Thank you for the opportunity.
Hi. If I wanted to apply
for a temporary position
for this weekend...
Is this your resume?
- No, it's not.
- Wow, this is impressive.
My only... copy.
Well, you are definitely
gonna get hired.
In fact, I'm gonna
call them right now.
Right now?
Yeah.
- Lola...
- Mm-hmm?
if I wanted to shop for,
say, a jacket...
Uh, yeah, sure.
Just to the left over there.
Thank you so much.
Hi, yeah, we have
a very lovely young lady
down at the front desk.
Uh, she's going to be...
Well, well, well.
Look at what we got here.
You know,
if I wasn't a betting cat,
I'd say Tommy boy here
is trying to break
into the hotel.
That's sure what it looks like.
This here is our alley,
punk!
Which makes this our hotel!
Wait, hold up.
Are you trying
to break into our hotel?
Yo, guys, don't worry about it.
It was a big misunderstanding.
Right, Tom?
Are you laughing at me?
Now, I'm sure you know what
I do to cats that laugh at me.
Come on, boss!
Preach! Preach to him!
Now, I was about to,
if you would shut that grill
and let me handle this.
My bad, boss.
So, are you gonna answer me?
Oh, snap!
It's five-o! Drop and run!
- Oh, no, not again!
- Somebody pick me up,
- I can't run that fast!
- Hey, I'll see you again, Tom!
- Break yourself!
- Hey, get back here!
Phew!
Oh, yeah!
Welcome.
Thank you so much.
- You must be...
- Hi. Buongiorno.
Forester, Kayla.
I'm sorry in advance
about my resume,
but there was
a child downstairs
trying to spit their
Hubba Bubba under a table.
So I tore off a piece.
Good. I'm Terence Mendoza,
Events Manager.
And this is Mr. Henry Dubros.
- Hi.
- A pleasure.
He's our general manager.
And I assume that that's
the aquatics manager?
That's Goldie.
She has no official position
at the hotel. That's a fish.
That's the...
I must say, this is
a very impressive resume.
The Dorsey?
Oh. The Dorsey.
You know, I hate to name names,
but, uh, I will.
You must have known
Mrs. Josephine Pennybaker.
She was my mentor at Cornell.
It's an Ivy League school
founded in 1865
by Mr. Ezra Cornell.
That's where I got my master's.
I'm just sharing.
Of course I know
old Jojo Pennyfoot.
Yeah. What a hoot.
Pennyfoot?
Well, Miss Forester,
we'll cut to the chase.
As I'm sure you know,
we have
a very high-profile event
happening here this weekend.
Of course, I'm very aware
of Ben and Preeta's wedding.
Well, we need to hire additional
staff through the week.
But they must maintain
the level of service
guests of
the Royal Gate expect.
- Nonetheless.
- And I'll be honest,
it's not often we come across
a resume this distinguished.
Excuse me,
but this, this is just
a piece of paper.
If I'm gonna be worthy
of this institution,
you need to see me in...
action.
Are you gonna pick it up
or just leave it there?
Yes, sir.
Put it in the bin.
Terence.
She thought the fish
was the head of the department.
Really?
A fish can't even walk.
It can't even...
Terence.
You're hired.
- Really?
- Yes.
I mean, thank you.
Can you start today?
That's gonna be a tall order.
Mm... Very in demand.
Okay. Yeah, you know what?
I'm gonna pull some strings.
It's difficult,
but, yeah, no problem.
One other thing.
Uh, we will be asking
all temporary staff
to stay at the hotel
through the week
leading up to the wedding.
Uh, just so that we can be
available to guests
at a moment's notice.
Is that something
you'd be comfortable with?
Anything for this hotel.
No, it's better down.
10-4, good buddy.
Breaker, breaker, 1-9.
Go get 'em.
Hair's better up.
It's more professional.
Good morning.
Good morning, sir.
The Royal Gate
opened its doors in 1930
and was declared
a New York City landmark
- by 1962.
- Mm.
It's been through
two major renovations,
yet it remains the beacon
of service excellence.
This place has been host
to four presidents,
three popes, two kings,
one queen,
oh, and Drake.
There are 260 rooms,
104 suites, and 21 floors
of impeccable luxury.
The water pressure
is never below 50 PSI,
and our thread count
is never below 800.
- Button, please.
- Sorry, sir.
The spa is
top-of-the-line,
and our spin instructor won
the Tour de France. Twice.
Right.
This wedding
is the most prestigious event
the Royal Gate has hosted.
And it will be
a perfect success.
It has to be.
The positive press an event
of this magnitude can generate
is invaluable.
Would you stop that, please?
- The... Yeah, sir.
- Okay.
Yes. It's just,
it tends to ride up.
Our wedding menu
is being designed
by our very own Chef Jackie.
He's a rising star,
and whispers are
that Michelin agrees.
Hector!
Look alive, people.
Why do you hate me?
Who butchered these onions?
Who?
Oh, I don't know. Francois?
- We should leave.
- You're killing my career!
He's a bit tricky,
but he's an artist.
And we're lucky to have him.
And some people
may see anger, but me?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I see passion.
Do you hear that?
- Hear what?
- Your footsteps.
- Oh.
- Carrara marble.
This is Gavin, our doorman.
Master of small talk.
This is Kayla,
who recently worked
at the Dorsey Hotel in London.
Did she now?
Yes. And she'll be
helping us out this week.
Mm. I'm sure you'll
knock 'em dead, Kayla.
Morning!
That's Joy, the bell girl.
I'm convinced
she was raised by wolves.
- What?
- She's not important.
Okay.
But this glass atrium.
Oh, wow. Now that is something.
It's one of a kind.
I call it the "crowning jewel
of the Royal Gate."
This is Cameron, the barman.
Popping bottles.
Excuse me?
Don't spill any
on your Jordan 5s.
These are actually
retro reissues.
Obviously, it's the lace tips.
- NikeLab?
- Flight Club.
On Broadway.
I'm sorry to interrupt
your riveting TED Talk,
but why are you
pouring champagne
at 11 o'clock in the morning?
I was told to pour two glasses
for the VIPs that just arrived.
They're here?
- Yes, sir.
- Who's here?
The bride and groom.
Come with me.
Wow!
- Isn't it perfect?
- I love it.
Just as much as I did
last week when we visited.
All I care about
in the whole world
is that you're happy.
Think your dad's gonna like it?
You keep asking
what my dad thinks,
I'm gonna send him
on the honeymoon with you.
Clear the way,
coming through.
I sure hope room service
is open all night.
Right, Toots?
Ben, Preeta, welcome back
to the Royal Gate.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
It's a toast
to your upcoming nuptials.
It's so great to be back here.
Thank you very much.
- Appreciate it.
- Absolutely.
And thank you guys
for everything.
It's great to see you again,
Terence.
- Thank you very much.
- Mouse!
Oh, my God!
Spike, get back here!
- Hey! Hey!
- Oh, my gosh!
Simmer down, boy! Hey!
Get back here!
- I'm so sorry.
- It's no problem.
Sorry.
- A little jumpy, huh?
- Ooh.
I'm sorry,
he's a little animated.
Yeah, um...
Oh, she's so sweet.
Wow, you're really good
with animals.
Toots is usually really shy.
And by "shy," I mean,
she... She scratches
people's faces off.
- Oh.
- Oh. Well...
she can smell
a bona fide animal lover.
You know,
Kayla's new here
and I was just about
to explain to her that, uh...
we traditionally
have a no-pets policy...
- Oh, wow.
- ...but, uh, you know...
I would be delighted
to make an exception.
- Is your hand okay?
- It's fine.
Looks like
your hand's bleeding.
It's fine, it's perfect.
We've prepared a list
of some of the most
prestigious dog parks
in the area, and I think
the one on 11th Street
is particularly luxurious.
But are the people uptight?
Because... I mean,
do they yell at the dogs
for being off-leash?
- Spike, he's... he's... Yeah.
- You can just say it.
- He's disgusting.
- Yeah.
- He's disgusting?
- Huh?
There is one that I know about
that's behind
this falafel place on 17th.
It's not technically
a dog park,
but they let
their dogs off-leash
and they kinda
look out for each other.
It's pretty low-key.
That is amazing.
Thank you, Kayla.
- Thanks, Kayla.
- Yes. Thank you, Kayla.
Of course. Any time.
I just have to say, I follow
you guys on Instagram,
and you are
the cutest couple ever.
And that rock, whoa!
- Yes, well...
- Yeah.
Could see that thing
from outer space. Good job.
You know, you could see
our love from outer space.
Oh.
That was fantastic.
- Great. Thank you.
- Shall we?
- We shall.
- Come on, Tootsie.
Come on, Spike.
But in all seriousness,
is there a safe in the hotel?
It's a giant diamond.
Of course, of course.
How was the ride?
Very good,
thank you very much.
Not... Not to worry.
That's probably
a scream of delight.
You know, someone seeing
their beautiful room
for the first time.
It happens all the time.
Lola? Can you see them
to their room?
- Excuse me.
- Of course.
Leo is shaken to the core.
The mouse
ran right over his foot.
Look, Terence,
I've worked too frigging hard
to be saddled
with a bunch of inept...
Wonderful group of gifted
colleagues to have my career
tossed into a fish bucket
over some infestation.
Jackie,
Jackie, Jackie, Jackie.
I know the gravity
of this situation.
- And I will handle it.
- I'll catch it, sir.
Him. Or her.
It could be a female...
- I'm not gender biased
- No, no.
- and I don't want to go by...
- No, no, it's fine. It's gender-fluid now.
The point is, I will catch
that little mouse,
and I will be
discreet about it.
Okay. I need you to understand
the sensitivity of this matter.
- Yes.
- If a picture of this mouse is tweeted up
to insta-book-face
or the ticky-tock,
we will be ruined.
No, sir. We're not ruined,
because it's not gonna happen.
Okay? So, you guys
clear your heads about it.
That Rodentia is toast.
What are you doing?
Oh, my gosh, you scared me.
I scared you?
You know, you're the one
creeping around like a thief.
I am on a mouse hunt.
Thank you.
Need any help?
What? Because I'm...
I'm... I'm the new girl?
Well, obviously,
you haven't seen my resume.
It clearly states that
I am completely capable
of doing anything
that is required
to do that is needed
to be done here.
Oh, right.
And how hard can it be
to catch a little mouse?
Honestly, I wasn't
expecting you to say yes.
You know, you got that whole
independent vibe thing
going on,
and I don't
normally get involved
with how the new kids
do their jobs. So...
My name, um... My name is
Kayla. Yeah.
My mom calls me Kayla.
Oh, okay, Kayla.
Well, I doubt that mouse
catching is on your resume,
but if you do catch him,
you should come by
for a celebratory beverage.
Well, start popping another
bottle of champagne now,
because any minute now,
he's mine.
He's... One second.
What the...
Did someone leave their...
What is that?
The sign
of a worthy competitor.
Guess who's at the party?
Come on, man.
Have some self-respect.
You are in a dumpster
and Jerry's inside,
safe and warm.
Look at him.
Just scouting the room and
seeing what he can steal next.
Now, who's the cat
and who's the mouse?
Hey, let's get back in there
and smash that mouse up good.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Tom, my brother,
there's room for both cats
and mice to be happy.
Look, I'm sure if you asked
to share his food...
Share? You're lucky
the kids are watching, okay?
We're cats. Cats take!
Come on, he's just
an innocent little mouse.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Why're we always arguing?
We shouldn't be fighting,
we look alike.
Why are we doing this?
Look, how about we do
something different this time?
Why don't we let Tom
make up his own mind, okay?
Now, see, that is a good idea.
Tom, I believe in you.
What a sucker.
Now go make me proud, Tom.
Whoa!
Ahhh!
Life, do you hear me?
Give my creation life!
Launch the third swing!
...my creation life!
Go for Lone Wolf.
Who?
It's Kayla, sir.
Just trying on one of
those new code names.
Well, don't.
Have you located the room yet?
I'm continuing
to get noise complaints.
Yes, sir...
Well, no, sir, I haven't yet,
but I'm... I'm on it. Over.
Well, hurry up so you can get
back to finding that mouse.
And please, do not say "over."
This isn't Star Trek.
Takes all the fun
out of walkie-talkies.
I mean, what's the point, then?
I can still hear you.
I have eyes on the target,
sir, and I am moving north...
I'm moving toward the door.
Oh, no.
What did you do?
Who...
Wait a second, I know you.
I know you! You're the cat
from the park with the bike
and you tackled me.
Is this personal?
Is this some form
of revenge sabotage?
What are you... You're trying
to tell me something?
Okay. Two syllables.
One word. Is it a movie?
Is it a cartoon?
What's this? A pig?
A mouse?
A little mouse?
What? He was here, too?
Gosh, I gotta catch
that little disaster.
If I don't,
I'm gonna lose this job.
Wait a second.
You're a cat.
Can't you catch a mouse?
Isn't that in your DNA?
Huh.
You got a name?
That is really well done, Mot.
Tom?
You could be
in a lot of trouble for this.
I mean, just look at this mess.
So, what should we do
about this?
You wanna catch
a mouse together?
There could be
a big reward in it for you.
Sir, I instructed her
to get rid of an animal,
not find another.
Here's how I see it, sir.
We have a mouse problem
at this hotel,
so we could hire
an exterminator
to have him tramp up and down
this whole hotel,
just filling it with his poison
and alerting Ben and Preeta
to the possibility of vermin
at their wedding,
or we could leverage
millions of years
of predatory-prey evolution
and choose a more
subtle and eco-friendly
solution.
That's why I brought on Tom.
You brought on...
She's a temp. She doesn't
even have hiring power.
It's what we did
at the Dorsey, sir.
Really?
That is not what they did
at the Dorsey.
Why don't I ask
Mrs. Pennybaker?
Who...
wouldn't want you to ask
Mrs. Pennybaker
from the Dorsey?
Why don't I call her
right now, huh?
Absolutely not.
No one's calling anyone.
Word gets out that we're
thinking of hiring a cat,
well, the mouse problem
could leak.
And if word gets out that
we're refusing to hire a cat,
PETA will be here
before you can say
"discriminatory practices."
Mm-hmm.
You need to think
outside the box, Terence.
Could he wear a hat?
Excuse me, sir?
Could he wear a jaunty hat?
And, uh, perhaps a name tag?
I think that'd be adorable.
One second.
Sir, you, you can't be serious?
A hat?
As you can see,
he would love to wear a hat.
And a name tag.
Well, then I think this is a
creative and elegant solve, Kayla.
Thank you, sir. As do I.
That'll be all.
Thank you.
You gotta fix your name tag.
There you go.
Yeah.
You look good.
I figured out who you are.
Who am I?
You're one of
those millennials.
that thinks they can get
whatever they want
whenever they want
without working for it,
preferably with free shipping.
Who doesn't
like free shipping?
This is a cutthroat
$200 billion industry.
And I've clawed my way
all the way to the middle.
And I don't intend
on stopping there.
Okay?
You better hope
this little cat plan works.
Because if it doesn't,
I'll make sure you'll never
work in New York City again.
And that goes for you, too,
Tom. Yes, you.
Enjoy it
while it lasts because...
This is just a test, Tom.
Uh-uh.
He doesn't think
that we can do it.
Just like most people I know.
But you and I,
we're different, Tom.
We don't go down easy.
All right,
I'm gonna start in the lobby.
Tom?
Okay. All right. You done?
Ahhh!
Mm?
Listen here, kitty-cat,
I don't like being pounded.
Capiche?
I see you again,
I bash your head in.
Spike, get back here.
Saw you again!
Toots.
There you are, girl.
What were you doing?
I was looking all over for you.
Whew!
Tom, what are you doing
in the lobby?
Oh!
I see you becoming the hunter...
feeling the hunted.
Yeah, there we go.
Tracking the trail.
Yeah, you smell
those little paws. Yep.
My gosh, Tom.
I mean, be the predator. Yeah.
Oh.
Okay, why are you...
You're drawing a...
Look, I...
Oh. Tom, that is
a "wanted dead or alive..."
That is a stick figure
of a mouse
and your Es are backwards.
That's never gonna work.
- You're looking for a mouse?
- Gosh! Hi.
Yes, Joy. Yeah.
Well, have you checked the tiny
little door on the 10th floor?
At first, I thought, "Whoa, Joy, you
became really big. When did that happen?"
But then I saw another door
that was normal sized
and thought, "Okay, so one of
your eyeballs got small."
- But then I blinked a ton
- Yeah.
and realized, "No, Joy,
just this door was really small."
So, I cut up a towel to make tiny
little towels and left them here.
But now they're gone.
Thank you, Joy. You are
a fascinating creature.
Hmm.
Me, fascinating? I like that.
Listen here, punk.
You and I gotta chat...
What?
You want me to grab it?
Thank you.
Oh, wow. This is so detailed.
What kind of
tiny printer or...
And it's scented?
What the...
Listen here, Mr. Mouse.
Oh. Jerry.
I need this job.
So, simply put, this is a hotel
and you're a mouse. So,
you gotta go.
Well, if that's how
you feel about it,
I'll have to introduce you
to my enforcer.
Oh!
Oh, my gosh!
Oh.
No!
You do not get to beat up
my enforcer!
Open up the door!
Open up!
Let me in!
- Kayla!
- Argh!
What do you need,
sir?
Meet me in the bridal suite
immediately.
Right away, sir.
You figure out a solution
to get that mouse out of here.
Uh, come on in.
Hey, guys.
Sorry, it's sort of
the wedding situation room
up here.
Wow.
Ah!
Terence, you were right.
This simulator's amazing.
- Ah!
- It really replicates how bad I am at golf.
Oh, I see that.
I haven't seen this many
shanks since I was in prison.
White-collar crime, but, uh...
Baby, do you wanna
maybe take a little break?
Or if you wanna
do something together,
we can go
scuba diving in Tahiti.
We, uh, could go
hang gliding in the Alps.
Or, uh, we could go
to this alien planet
and just sort of,
uh, shoot some aliens.
Kayla, you could
just put those down. Sorry.
- Where? Here?
- Just right behind you.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
Terence, actually, could I
grab that one from you?
Ah, good. It's heavy.
Think this might be it.
Just a little bit of a
surprise for me and the Mrs.
Let's see.
By the way, while I have you,
Terence, um,
- could I ask you a question?
- Absolutely.
What do you think
about elephants?
Um... Elephants.
I think they are majestic
and noble creatures.
No, I mean for the wedding.
Oh, at the wedding?
Real elephants?
Yeah, I sort of thought
it might be fun.
Babe, I never said
that they wouldn't be fun.
Oh...
So, uh, maybe, you know...
Maybe we'll do elephants.
Maybe we do elephants.
Have you, um,
considered maybe
a smaller animal like a...
- like a hamster?
- Hamster?
- Oh. That's cute.
- Yeah.
We were gonna
ride in on it, though.
Can, can you ride a hamster?
Oh, yes. I mean, as long
as you have enough of them,
- you can ride them silly.
- Yes.
Great. Yeah.
Well, that's something
to consider, too.
Babe, if getting elephants
at the wedding
would make you happy...
You being happy
would make me happy.
Aw!
Okay, get the elephants.
All right!
We're gonna get the elephants.
Great! We'll do the elephants!
Boom.
Oh! It's a motorized
skateboard. I love those.
It's got, uh, you know, Wi-Fi.
Why does a skateboard
need Wi-Fi?
Why the fi not?
"Why the fi not?"
See what I'm dealing with?
Oh.
Hello? Hey.
- Yeah, uh, he's right here.
- Who is it?
My dad.
What? Do I look okay?
For a phone call? Yes.
Right.
One second. Phew.
Hello, Mr. Mehta.
You sound like
you look amazing.
Uh-huh?
- If you need anything at all, please don't hesitate to call.
- Yeah.
We'll help you accordingly.
You know what, Terence,
Spike got into some burritos
- earlier and, well...
- Huh?
I was, you know. Do you mind?
Um... Of course.
I'm ready! I'm ready!
Thank you.
Kayla, can you...
Uh, actually,
I would love to keep Kayla
and maybe run through
some bridesmaids-related stuff
with her.
- You know, coordinating colors.
- Sure.
I have a very good eye.
No, that's fine. I'll just
run through it all with Kayla.
Here we go. I got the lead.
I got the lead. Come on.
Very well.
- Of course.
- Thank you, Terence.
- Kayla.
- Yes.
Wow, what a view!
So, what are
your bridesmaids colors?
I lost my ring.
The big one?
Yeah, my big one.
My... My only one.
How?
Well, I was,
I was on my way to the spa,
and Ben had told me
to put it in the safe
because he's always convinced
that I'm gonna lose it.
But you did lose it.
Yeah, I mean, I misplaced it.
I thought first someone
must've taken it, but...
And would you say
that it is still in the spa?
Or the pool.
Or the lounge. I was
all over the place today,
but I don't want Ben to know
that it was ever missing.
Really? I mean,
won't he just be all adorable
and understanding about it?
Babe,
that was a really big ring.
- Ah. Understood.
- Hey.
Hi.
- Hi.
- What did my dad want?
Nothing. He was just, uh,
we were just kinda bonding.
Great.
Uh, where is your ring?
Which ring?
Your engagement ring?
The giant one
that I gave you for love.
Oh, um... I...
Uh, the thing is...
It's a funny story
actually, sir.
I actually took it.
Yes, I did.
- To go get cleaned.
- Oh.
I took it to go get
a scrub-a-dub
and be all shiny
for the wedding.
Bright as bright as a diamond.
Great. That's actually
very thoughtful.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Kayla.
By the way, we really wanna put
some kind of gratuity
for you on the bill.
Whatever you see fit, sir.
- Thanks.
- Love you, guys.
- Love you.
- In different ways.
Thank you.
Anytime.
Whoop. Excuse me.
Come on, come on, come on.
Stop, stop! Stop!
Ow!
- No, no, no, wait, wait!
- Uh-oh.
- What?
- Here it comes.
Are you okay?
- Oh, yes.
- No, no, no!
Oh, come on!
Stop the beeping! You're
making him self-conscious!
How many burritos
did you eat?
Oh!
I see what you did.
Okay.
I'm scooping the poop, huh?
You saw he did it on purpose...
Let's go!
Joy?
Hey, Kayla,
oh, how's the mouse hunt going?
Oh, it's going.
By the way,
quick question for you.
Say a VIP person lost a ring
and someone wanted
to look for said ring
without raising any eyebrows,
where would you say
that person should look?
Oh, my God, I, I,
I love riddles. Um...
Well, if I were that someone,
ah, but I'm not.
But I could be. Who knows?
One day. One can only dream.
VIP.
Sorry, back to the question.
Um...
It would depend
on the size of the object.
Is it a car? Is it alive?
Could it be a dog?
I lose things all the time.
I lost my baby brother
last week.
Don't tell anyone, please,
because I was like,
"Joey, where are you? Please?"
And then, thank the Lord, he...
Yeah.
Tom! What?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, chill out!
Besides, that is never gonna
keep out
that minuscule sociopath.
What do you mean, he's gone?
Like, like gone-gone?
Are you sure?
Yes! Booyah, Tom! Oh!
♪ More hot milk
for you tonight ♪
Boom!
Mr. Dubros,
I am delighted to inform you
that the job
that we hired Tom for,
- it is completed.
- Oh, wonderful.
Now we just have to figure out
how to let him go
without triggering
an equal employment issue.
Oh.
I should probably look into
severance packages.
- Right.
- Maybe a month of tuna?
- 'Cause he's a cat.
- Mm-hmm.
I think
it's one per family.
And if there's any way to make
sure the guests get these
as soon as they check in...
The bride's taken
quite a shine to you.
I don't know, I mean,
whatever I can do to help
with the wedding craziness.
They seem really stressed out
with it all.
If anything, the ceremony
is the perfect test
for a relationship.
'Cause you can promise
all you want in the vows.
When it comes down to it,
it's how you handle
the pressure of the planning.
Some couples rise to
the challenge and others fall.
Hmm. I should write that down.
So, did Tom tell you
the good news?
The mouse problem
has officially been handled.
Hey! She came, she saw,
she exterminated.
Yeah.
So, how about we celebrate?
Flat club soda coming right up.
Yeah, there we go.
The real wild stuff.
Wow, those little paws
move quick, huh?
You should be his manager.
I mean, sure, why not?
Maybe they'll see
how much I'm killing it
and bring me on permanently
to run everything?
Okay, so somebody thinks
they can skip a few steps.
Mm-mm.
No, it's just...
I mean,
where I came from,
there were
no real opportunities.
Where's that?
A small town in Penn State.
Picture seeing
your whole future
in front of you
and you can't stand it.
That was me, there.
I just wanted to find that
thing that made me feel...
Important?
Yeah.
And New York seemed like the
right place to look for it.
Well, I mean,
I've heard about your resume.
About that...
Hey, come on, don't be shy.
Whatever shot you're
looking for, you deserve.
You know, you're proof
that it takes more than
a fancy resume
to make it big in New York.
Right?
Guilty as charged.
Toots needs
a little pawpicure.
Kayla mentioned
you might have a spot.
We could actually see her right now.
That would be so great.
♪ Whoo ♪
♪ Well ♪
♪ Don't you know, baby ♪
♪ Child, don't you know, baby ♪
♪ Oh, don't you know, baby ♪
♪ Little girl, little girl,
Don't you know, oh ♪
♪ Please listen to me, baby ♪
- ♪ Girl, I'm in love With you so ♪
- Yeah
♪ Turn your lamp down low ♪
♪ I said turn
Your lamp down low ♪
♪ Whoo ♪
♪ Turn it down ♪
♪ Please turn your lamp down ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪
Okay, come on, baby.
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
Oh, my gosh.
No, no, no. Stop it.
Both of you.
Why is he alive?
Why is he here?
It's over, Jerry.
I'm calling in the poison guys.
Why do you have Preeta's ring?
Have you had it
this entire time?
Give it to me.
Now. Drop the ring.
What do you want for it, Jerry?
You wanna stay here?
You little con artist.
Fine. We can discuss this
on my terms.
Okay, no problem!
I got it!
Tom...
- Excuse me!
- Where did he go?
- Tom, where did he go?
- Find him. Now.
- Stop. I said, stop!
Stop! Stop!
Calmate!
I'm the boss.
Why do I see temporary
employees socializing
on hotel property
in the middle of their shift?
We were just...
Terence, we're celebrating,
you know?
The, uh, hotel's mouse problem
is taken care of.
Oh, yeah, congratulations.
Teamwork is dream work, right?
Yeah, it's taken care of,
right, Tom?
It is
so taken care of, right, Tom?
What... What is he doing?
He's not doing nothing.
- Why are you acting nervous?
- Huh?
You're acting nervous.
I'm not acting nervous.
No? What's in your pocket?
Ah.
- Oh.
- Terence.
- Wait! No, he's in the pocket.
- Terence, what are you doing?
The mouse
is in the pocket.
Come back here!
Oh!
Oh, I'm so sorry!
Whoa!
Come here, pussycat.
Everyone, keep calm!
Oh, no!
Ooh.
The mouse!
Huh? Whoa!
Oh...
What the...
Oh.
This is definitely your bad.
Kayla,
and what would you call this, huh?
This was a mistake.
It was
a total misunderstanding.
This is a dereliction of duty!
And it's a reflection
of the absence of character!
It's an embarrassment
to the hotel.
And it's an insult to you.
That's how serious
this matter is, sir.
I agree.
Terence,
I'm placing you on leave.
What?
It's clear that the magnitude
of this wedding
has overwhelmed you and you're
in something of a state.
- I think a break would...
- Hold on a sec. Let me make sure
that we're
on the same page here
regarding
the basic facts of this.
The cat
that she forced us to hire
failed to catch the mouse.
Kayla said
she got rid of the mouse.
Isn't that right?
- That is what I said.
- Ah!
That is what you said.
But that is not what you did.
The mouse that caused all that
destruction to our lobby
is still in the hotel.
I saw him
in the animal tornado.
Terence, listen to yourself.
No one saw a mouse.
I saw the mouse.
But they did see you
acting erratically
towards Miss Forester
after bringing the groom's
bulldog into a bar.
She brought the kitty-cat
to the bar, too.
Tom is an employee.
He has a name tag.
This is insane.
I'm going insane right now.
Well, you're certainly
acting insane.
You caused tens of
thousands of dollars of damage
to the hotel,
you've terrified our guests,
and now you're attempting
to frame it as Kayla's fault?
You know what?
You can't do this.
You can't fire
the event manager
in the middle of an event.
Please leave
on your own merits, Terence.
I don't want
to have to call security.
Please don't do this.
Oh.
Okay.
Argh!
Oh, my days.
And I'm not picking it up.
Get your tail out of your ears.
It's disgusting.
Well, this is a disaster.
Yeah.
Firing our events manager
before the biggest
and most important event
this hotel has thrown in years.
The only reason
I felt comfortable
asking Terence to take leave
is because we have someone
with your wealth
of experience here.
With the what now?
I got a call from Miss Preeta.
She told me
that you quietly found
a very important missing item
she was looking for.
You're multitalented, Kayla.
Do you think you can handle
the role
of interim event manager?
Are you kidding?
Yes, yes, of course.
It's a massive endeavor.
Sir, "massive endeavor"
is my middle name.
It's Judith,
but you get the point.
I know you're new,
but your employment history
convinces me
you're qualified
to take this on.
And who knows,
if this weekend goes well,
we may be discussing a more
permanent position on Monday.
I can't imagine... anything
that could
possibly mess this up.
Stop it.
You guys gotta stop fighting.
It's like you've been
doing this for years.
Listen, first of all,
thank you for the ring.
Helpful to have it back
after you stole it.
Never mind.
Remember when I said
to the both of you
that letting you stay here
wasn't up to me?
Well,
if you look right there,
I'm in charge now, all right?
And this wedding
it's a huge responsibility.
It's the shot
that I've been waiting for
and I can't screw it up.
So, you two, you gotta go.
Stop looking at me like that.
Ugh! Okay.
Maybe you can stay here.
But not like this.
Uh-uh. That little mess
you caused downstairs,
it's a disaster.
You know what,
you wanna stay, right?
Fine. One condition.
You two have to prove to me
that you can coexist together.
And stay as far away
from here as possible.
Got it?
So, tomorrow,
I'm gonna plan an entire day
for you two to spend together
out there, in the Big Apple.
And if you do this,
you guys can stay.
Do we have a deal?
Your car will be here
at 9:00 a.m.
Don't be late.
Okay, guys,
please, everyone...
Uh...
Please...
Any, any true emergencies?
True emergencies?
Let's just go around the room
one at a time.
I just caught
my finger in the door and...
Okay, please,
seriously, just shut up, please. Uh...
Madam Kaydra,
are we sure the mouse is gone?
Rumors are
the guest list includes
a Michelin
restaurant inspector,
so one slip-up
and me and my son
are out on the streets.
Jackie, rest assured,
the mouse is currently
being taken care of.
Anyone else have
any other problems?
Uh, did you address
the, um, elephant that's here?
Cameron,
yes, I addressed
the elephant in the room.
You weren't here for it.
Yeah, no, I mean literally.
Where do you want 'em?
Um...
Pardon. The elephants?
Can't leave 'em in the truck.
No. That would be inhumane.
- They can be parked at valet.
- Okay.
Relax, Cecil.
Okay. How about we go ahead and put
all the birds in the staff room?
Um, the animal wrangler
said this time of year
they need room
to socialize and mate.
I think they've
socialized enough, Joy.
This is a wedding after all,
not spring break.
- Ca-caw!
- So let's just go ahead
and put 'em in the staff room.
What...
What sound do peacocks make?
- I mean...
- Ca-caw!
I think that sounds right.
Kayla, come on already.
Oh, gosh, I so regret
saying yes to this.
Pa-pa-pam-pam!
Oh, my God.
You look incredible.
Thank you.
Well, we are
a full-service hotel here.
Be it dog walking,
or quite even possibly,
saving someone's lost ring.
Hmm.
Is there anything else
I can help you with, milady?
Oh, no, thank you.
This wedding
is bonkers enough already.
Why don't you just say no?
Oh, no, we've...
We've just decided
to, um, avoid behaviors
that might give the impression
that we're fighting.
But what about
when it's just you two?
I mean, we disagree, of course,
about how big
- the wedding should be.
- Wow.
But I guess there was so much
pressure to maintain an image
that somewhere
we forgot how to fight.
Ben really loves you, Preeta.
Yeah. He's a really good guy.
It's just that when he goes,
he goes big.
And I love that about him.
Yeah.
But I have
this feeling that this
small Indian wedding is gonna
be a great big disaster.
Beautiful day
at Yankee Stadium.
Top of the 9th inning, two out,
and the Yankees up by one.
Big Alex Gordon at the plate.
That ball is crushed.
This might be it.
The ball game may be over.
The Yankees
could move on and...
Oh! What's this?
A hairy fan has reached over and caught the ball.
Mayhem
unfolds at Yankee Stadium.
Two baseball fans
seated in right field
interrupted
what could have been
the final out for the Yankees.
The culprits were later
taken away by animal control.
In other news...
Oh, my gosh!
What was...
Ben, was that a drone?
Not just any drone.
That was a CH-4000,
military-grade.
- Yeah.
- But I'm sure it's harmless.
Joy?
- Should I go see what that...
- Yes. Yes, Joy.
- Oh, okay. Going.
- Yes, Joy, go. Yep.
That was a scream.
It's harmless.
Yeah.
Military things usually are.
I got this drone
because I thought,
uh, when Preeta and I come into
the wedding on the elephants,
that the drone
could be kind of, uh...
As I'm saying the words
"drone" and "elephant,"
out loud
to another human being,
I'm wondering, is this, um...
is this a lot?
Weddings, Ben,
they're already
stressful enough,
- you know?
- Yeah.
The important part
is that Preeta,
she can't wait to marry you.
So, just take it easy,
you know?
Enjoy the ride.
- Yeah.
- You only got one shot at it.
Like, one chance to,
like, get it right.
Uh-huh. So just go ahead
and pull it back.
Yeah. Pull it back
and just sorta let it rip.
Like, really,
just pull it way back
and just explode out of it.
That is not what I was
- trying to say to you.
- Yeah.
They said they'd
disabled the weapons.
- There's weapons?
- Uh, I'll make sure.
I found it.
I found the...
Oh, my God!
Help me, help me, help me!
She found it.
Don't look it in the eyes, Joy.
Welcome to your new home,
gentlemen.
Hey, hey, hey, pipe down!
You already been fed.
Hello.
Quiet.
Get comfortable.
You're gonna be here a while.
Have a nice stay!
♪ Alley cats ♪
♪ Come out and play ♪
That's that cat
from the alley!
Well, well, well.
So, we meet again.
You know, you and me?
We got some
unfinished business to settle.
Dinner time.
Snack is what
I like to call it.
Relax, you two.
This won't take long,
as long as you don't fight it.
Gotcha.
Oh, don't be scared,
come here!
Are you gonna eat him?
Why don't you be a good
little kitty and hand him over
before I stop being nice?
Yeah, what are you, like,
friends or something?
Go ahead. Eat him now.
If we can't eat him,
you gotta eat him.
Looks like
a nice snack.
Chew. Chew.
- Eat him. Eat. Eat.
- Chew. Chew. Chew.
- Eat it.
- Chew. Chew.
Ah, ah,
there you go. Bottoms up!
- Eat him!
- There you go!
Is it as good
as it looks?
What are you waiting for? Chew.
Chew. Chew.
Chew. Chew. Chew. Chew.
If you don't start chewing,
we will.
Oh, that's spicy.
Cajun.
Chew. Chew. Chew.
Wait a minute. Something
ain't right. Open your mouth.
You heard him,
open your trap!
Hey, cat.
You got a visitor.
- What?
- Visitors?
He didn't even eat him!
Mouse, you got one, too.
Hola, Tom.
How are they treating you?
This place is, uh, horrible.
Cheese stick?
Oh, you don't want it?
Here's the deal.
I know you wanna
come back to the hotel,
and I can help you do it.
As you may already know,
Kayla's been put
in charge of the wedding.
And, yeah, it's a tough job.
That's why she sent me here
to bring you back.
So you can help.
But there's a catch.
I can only take one of you.
You know what your friend said?
That it's your fault.
Maybe I shouldn't say this,
you know?
He says you smell like...
Like tuna.
And a cheesy foot.
He also said that you're, uh...
You're emotionally unavailable.
He also wants
you to stay here and rot.
Now, you put me
in such a tough position.
As you already know,
I can only take one of you
back to the hotel.
Will it be the cat?
Or the mouse?
Okay.
I've made my decision.
Check this out.
In celebrity news,
major commotion at the Royal Gate Hotel
as New York's elite couple,
Preeta and Ben,
are tying the knot in
a private, intimate wedding.
Ah... Ah...
Ta-da!
Okay.
No, no. No, no, no.
Move.
Mr. Mehta, what do you think?
You're not wearing a turban.
Is that, Is that a question
or a statement?
I didn't know
if you wanted an answer.
I've been getting
really into cricket!
You're doing great.
How are we doing
on the champagne?
We good, we good.
There's just a lot of it,
and not enough hands.
Okay.
All right, bro.
Take these upstairs.
I'll be up in a minute.
You good?
Yeah, yeah. I think so.
Momma bird,
we got a problem here. We need you.
Okay, on my way.
- Hmm.
- What?
I think I might have
just pulled this off.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the ceremony is about to begin.
All right, Malcolm,
game face, look impressive.
FYI, I'm always ready.
LOL.
Ben, this feels
so embarrassing.
Well, if it's any consolation,
you look very beautiful.
And in a way,
you know, we're the elephants.
Because we're never
gonna forget this wedding.
Here we go.
Wow!
Preeta!
Wow.
The, the elephant are normal
in these kind of events?
We are an elephant-friendly
establishment.
Friendly establishment.
Wow.
That's really beautiful.
The elephants
were a great choice.
Welcome back.
Consider this wedding
a welcome party.
Just for you.
Oh, no.
No.
What is Jerry doing here?
Well, that must be awkward.
With all the horrible things
he said about you.
That you're not fit
to work at the Royal Gate.
Tom, come on, now.
Let's not be insensitive.
Oh, would you just
leave him alone already?
Well, I got something to say.
Okay, go ahead and speak, then!
As I was saying...
Gotcha!
Now let's go finish
what we started.
Have fun.
Why is Tom here?
What the...
I don't see Jerry.
Do you see Jerry?
Uh, no. I don't.
- Hi. Hey.
- Hi.
Isn't this great?
And look, your dad loves it.
At least,
I think he's loving it.
It's kinda hard to tell.
Not bad.
Ah. Smile for the drone-cam.
Drone-cam?
Yeah. They can put
a cam on a drone.
Wait. Are those peacocks?
Yeah, I think they might
have just been
part of the, uh,
exotic bird package.
And, and even the tiger?
Well, the tiger is our first.
I begged you
to stop doing this stuff.
I'm sorry.
That is the last surprise.
You just don't listen.
Listen to what?
Hmm?
No, Tom. Don't do it.
Do it, Tom. Do it.
You're dead, mouse.
Yes!
OMG. Is that a mouse?
WT...
Preeta!
Mouse! Mouse!
Mouse, mouse, mouse,
mouse, mouse!
- We got him.
- Oh, my baby!
No, no. Stay calm, everyone!
Mouse! Ahh!
Mouse! Mouse!
Mouse! Ah, mouse!
Ugh. Get off.
You?
No. Me.
Mouse, mouse,
mouse, mouse, mouse!
Mouse!
Please remain calm.
Out of my way!
Malcolm!
I'm coming to save you!
Oh, no!
Huh? Oh.
Preeta!
Out the back door.
Let's get out of here!
Oh, no!
Cecil! Malcolm!
Stop! Stop!
What is he doing here?
Terence is here
because he tried to warn me
about Kayla, who clearly lied
about who she is.
No, sir. Uh, this was a misunderstanding.
It was, um...
No.
Actually, it wasn't
a misunderstanding.
Sir, when I came
into your office that day,
I had stolen
someone else's resume...
and pretended that it was mine.
I don't have
any qualifications for this.
Or for anything, really.
You not only
destroyed this wedding,
but may have destroyed
the future of this hotel.
I'm sorry.
Perhaps I could salvage this.
Don't bother.
I just came here
to inform Mr. Dubros
that the wedding's off.
Preeta.
Oh...
I guess we were both
in over our heads.
I...
Kayla, I don't get
why you just...
I was gonna tell you, Cameron.
I was gonna tell
all of you the truth.
I just wanted to prove to
you all that I deserved this.
That I could do this.
I'm sorry.
And don't even
think about coming back.
You think I was gonna
let some street animals
live at the Royal Gate Hotel?
Oh, no.
Hey.
Thanks for meeting me.
I know I wasn't
very convincing yesterday.
But what I was trying to say
was, I really am sorry.
I still can't believe
that I saw everything
that woman accomplished
on her resume,
and I thought that my pure
ambition was an even swap.
Come on, Kayla,
everybody screws up.
It's just hard.
I mean, every morning I wake up
and I look at my phone,
and my newsfeed
is filled with people
who are our age,
you know, they're succeeding
at what they're doing.
Well, maybe we just need
to stop comparing ourselves
to everybody
and just work for it.
Listen, Kayla,
you're gonna get the skills.
You already got the smarts,
you got the funny,
and you got the love
of helping people.
Even if I wanted to make
this right, I couldn't.
Well, maybe they
can help
convince you otherwise.
No.
You two are the last people
that I wanna see right now.
What is all this?
I think that's Preeta and Ben.
All right, you know what? Just cut the
chalkboard act and tell me what's going on.
Okay, you and Jerry
have an idea for what?
How did you...
Elephants?
Ca-caw!
And peacocks? A big cake?
Guys, are you
just making fun of me?
Oh, so, this is like charades?
No.
'Cause he did like a...
No? All right, never mind.
I think what they're
trying to tell us
is that if we go back
to the hotel,
quickly salvage what we can,
and we find a last-minute venue
and some sort
of befitting celebrant,
we can fix this by putting on
a makeshift wedding.
And you got
all of that from that?
Yeah.
We kinda understand
each other now.
Let's do it.
What do we have to lose?
Hey.
Where's Preeta going?
A doorman never tells.
JFK.
Okay, guys. I know that
you both don't get along,
but now it's time
to change that.
So, help me save this wedding
and go catch that bride, okay?
And bring her back here.
What do you want?
I just need to talk to Ben
for a minute.
No, don't you think
you've done enough?
Ben. This wedding
can still happen, today.
How? I mean,
everything's destroyed.
It doesn't matter.
Preeta never actually
wanted any of this.
She just wanted
you to listen to her.
I, I don't think so.
Wait. Someone once told me
that a wedding
is a couple's very first test.
And some couples,
well, they rise to that.
Stupid.
What kind of idiot said that?
- I mean, seriously...
- Me.
Oh.
I apologize. I'm sorry.
I was being, uh, sarcastic.
You can rise, Ben.
We can still pull this off.
Needless to say,
everything at this hotel
will be at your disposal.
Except, of course, the hotel.
What about the garden
across the street?
Uh, I'm sorry, garden?
Mm-hmm.
Wait, do you mean Central Park?
Sure. Whatever nickname
you have for it.
That's actually
an amazing idea.
Joy, thank you.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Well, how about, Terence,
you and Ben
get a guest list together,
and then let everyone know
where to meet us?
You expect me to assist you
after what you've done
to this hotel?
I think we both did some things
that we regret
to keep our jobs.
Tom and Jerry
told me what you did.
I'm not gonna tell anybody.
Okay, thank you.
If Tom and Jerry can be
out there working together,
then so can we.
Roger, roger, over.
Come in, Tom and Jerry.
I know you can't talk,
but I'm sure you can hear me.
Preeta's on Lexington,
and it looks like she's headed
for the Midtown Tunnel.
No, wait, they're actually
making a left turn on 57th.
They're going for
the Queensboro Bridge.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Guys, you have to get them
before they make it
to the bridge.
Hello?
Ugh, this no-talking thing
is really getting old.
Whoa!
Toots!
Stop the car!
Follow them. Let's go.
Could you keep up?
Great job, guys.
I'm sending you
a new location.
Toots.
Come back!
What...
Kayla, what is going on?
Hear me out.
I know
yesterday was a disaster.
But I promise you
that most of the chaos
was because of me.
And them.
But just like me,
they've changed their ways.
But, Preeta,
I really think we have
the chance to make this right.
Good luck.
Listen, Preeta, I'm sorry.
Okay? I wanted to give you
the wedding of your dreams,
but at some point,
it drifted into my dreams
and your father's dreams,
and then your father
was in my dreams,
and in one of them,
he was riding a tiger.
It was really weird.
And then...
I'm sorry that
I didn't just shut up
and listen to what you wanted.
What I want is you.
It's only ever been that.
Going forward,
I promise fewer surprises,
and I promise more truth.
'Cause honestly,
I love you.
Will you please take this back?
And will you marry me again,
but better this time?
You know, it wasn't
all Thomas and Jerome.
I know you had
a hand in it, too.
You were right
from the beginning.
A resume
is just a piece of paper.
You have to give
someone a chance
to find out what they can do.
I agree.
Yes, you, um,
did a very good job.
Thank you, Terence.
On that note,
I would love to introduce you
to Miss Linda Perrybottom.
Mr. Dubros.
The real owner of the resume.
Hello.
You must be Terence.
Uh, I am.
Josephine Pennybaker
at the Dorsey
says the most wonderful things
about you.
Oh, she does?
It's quite
an impressive resume.
Um...
I guess I'll see you
in my office tomorrow, or,
um, in Mr. Dubros' office
tomorrow.
Thank you, Kayla.
And we'll see you tomorrow.
Thank you, sir.
And I won't let you down.
Good luck, Terence.
All right, I think we actually
might've pulled this off,
maybe.
Oh, definitely.
- Champagne.
- Mm-hmm.
Cheers.
Huh?
Come here, pussycat.
You're ruining the whole day.
I'm gonna
turn you into a biscuit.
Huh?
Sorry. Nothing to see here.
What the...
Maybach music...
Uh, Mr. Dubros, I just
got a bill for both weddings.
That's a joke, right?
Well, you know, I, uh,
had Terence run some numbers
earlier and...
it doesn't look good for you.
Thank you for choosing
the Royal Gate.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull