Once upon a time there
was a lovely princess.
But she had an enchantment
upon her of a fearful sort...
which could only be broken
by love's first kiss.
She was locked away
in a castle...
guarded by a terrible
fire-breathing dragon.
Many brave knights had attempted to
free her from this dreadful prison,
but none prevailed.
She waited in the dragon's
keep...
in the highest room of
the tallest tower...
for her true love and
true love's first kiss.
Like that's ever gonna happen.
What a load of...
Somebody once told me the
world is gonna roll me
I am not the sharpest
tool in the shed
She was looking kind of dumb
with her finger and her thumb
In the shape of an L
on her forehead
The years start coming and
they don't stop coming
Fed to the rules and
I hit the ground running
Didn't make sense not
to live for fun
Your brain gets smart but
your head gets dumb
So much to do, so much to see
So what's wrong with
taking the backstreets
You'll never know
if you don't go
You'll never shine
if you don't glow
Hey, now, you're an all-star
Get your game on, go play
Hey, now, you're a rock star,
get the show on, get paid
And all that glitters is gold
Only shooting stars
break the mould
It's a cool place and
they say it gets colder
You're bundled up now but
wait till you get older
But the meteor men
beg to differ
Judging by the hole in
the satellite picture
The ice we skate is
getting pretty thin
The water's getting warm
so you might as well swim
My world's on fire,
how about yours
That's the way I like it
and I'll never get bored
Hey, now, you're an all-star
Get your game on, go play
Hey, now, you're a rock star,
get the show on, get paid
And all that glitters is gold
Only shooting stars
break the mould
- Go!
Go. Go. Go.
Hey, now, you're an all-star
Get your game on, go play
Hey, now, you're a rock star,
get the show on, get paid
And all that glitters is gold
Only shooting stars
break the mould
- Think it's in there?
- All right. Let's get it!
Whoa. Hold on. Do you know
what that thing can do to you?
Yeah, it'll grind your
bones for its bread.
Yes, well, actually,
that would be a giant.
Now, ogres...
they're much worse.
They'll make a suit from
your freshly peeled skin.
- No!
- They'll shave your liver.
Squeeze the jelly
from your eyes!
- Actually, it's quite good on toast.
- Back! Back, beast!
Back! I warn ya!
Right.
This is the part where
you run away.
And stay out!
Wanted. Fairy tale creatures.
All right. This one's full.
Take it away!
- Move it along. Come on! Get up!
- Next!
Give me that!
Your flying days are over.
That's 20 pieces of silver
for the witch. Next!
- Get up! Come on!
- Twenty pieces.
Sit down there!
Keep quiet!
This cage is too small.
Please don't turn me in. I'll
never be stubborn again.
I can change. Please!
Give me another chance!
- Oh, shut up.
- Next!
- What have you got?
- This little wooden puppet.
I'm not a puppet.
I'm a real boy.
Five shillings for
the possessed toy.
- Take it away.
- Father, please! Don't let them do this!
- Next. What have you got?
- Help me!
Well, I've got a talking donkey.
Right. Well, that's good for ten
shillings, if you can prove it.
Oh, go ahead, little fella.
Well?
Oh, he's just...
he's just a little nervous.
He's really quite a chatterbox.
Talk, you bone headed dolt...
- That's it. I've heard enough. Guards!
- No, no, he talks!
He does.
I can talk. I love to talk.
I'm the talkingest damn
thing you ever saw.
- Get her out of my sight.
- No, no!
I swear! He can talk!
Hey! I can fly!
- He can fly!
- He can talk!
- That's right, fool!
Now I'm a flying,
talking donkey.
You might have seen a house fly,
maybe even a super fly,
but I bet you ain't never
seen a donkey fly.
Seize him!
After him! He's getting away!
Get him! This way! Turn!
You there. Ogre!
Aye?
By the order of Lord
Farquaad, I am...
authorised to place you
both under arrest...
and transport you to a designated
resettlement facility.
Oh, really?
You and what army?
Can I say something to you?
Listen, you was really, really
something back there. Incredible!
Are you talking to me?
Yes, I was talking to you.
Can I just tell you
that you was great back there?
Those guards!
They thought they was all of that.
Then you showed up, and bam!
They was tripping over themselves
like babes in the woods.
That really made me
feel good to see that.
- Oh, that's great. Really.
- Man, it's good to be free.
Now, why don't you go celebrate your
freedom with your own friends? Hmm?
But I don't have any friends.
And I'm not going out
there by myself.
Hey, wait a minute! I got a great idea!
I'll stick with you.
You're a mean, green,
fighting machine.
Together we'll scare the spit
out of anybody that crosses us.
Oh, wow! That was
really scary.
If you don't mind me saying,
if that don't work,
your breath certainly
will get the job done,
'cause you definitely need some Tic Tacs
or something, 'cause your breath stinks!
You almost burned the
hair outta my nose,
just like the time...
Then I ate some rotten berries. I had
strong gases eking out of my butt that day.
Why are you following me?
I'll tell you why.
'Cause I'm all alone
There's no one here beside me
My problems have all gone
There's no one to deride me
But you gotta have friends...
Stop singing!
It's no wonder you don't
have any friends.
Only a true friend would be
that truly honest.
Listen, little donkey.
Take a look at me. What am I?
- Really tall?
- No! I'm an ogre.
You know. Grab your torch
and pitchforks.
Doesn't that bother you?
Nope.
- Really?
- Really, really.
Man, I like you.
What's your name?
Shrek.
Shrek? Well, you know what
I like about you, Shrek?
You got that kind of...
I-don't-care-what-nobody
thinks-of-me thing.
I like that. I respect that, Shrek.
You all right.
Look at that. Who'd want to live
in a place like that?
That would be my home.
And it is lovely!
Just beautiful.
You are quite a decorator. It's amazing
what you've done with such a modest budget.
I like that boulder.
That is a nice boulder.
I guess you don't
entertain much, do you?
I like my privacy.
You know, I do too. That's
another thing we have in common.
Like, I hate it when you
got somebody in your face.
You're trying to give them a
hint, and they won't leave.
There's that awkward silence.
- Can I stay with you?
- What?
Can I stay with you, please?
- Of course!
- Really?
- No.
- Please! I don't wanna go back there!
You don't know what it's like to be
considered a freak. Well, maybe you do.
But that's why we gotta stick together.
You gotta let me stay!
- Please! Please!
- Okay! Okay!
- But one night only.
- Thank you!
- What are you... No! No!
- This is gonna be fun!
We can stay up late,
swapping manly stories,
and in the morning
I'm making waffles.
Where do I sleep?
Outside!
Oh, well, I guess that's cool.
I mean, I don't know you,
and you don't know me,
so I guess outside
is best, you know.
Here I go.
Good night.
I mean, I do like the outdoors.
I'm a donkey.
I was born outside.
I'll just be sitting by myself
outside, I guess, you know.
By myself, outside.
I'm all alone, there's
no one here beside me.
I thought I told you
to stay outside.
I am outside.
Well, gents, it's a far cry from the
farm, but what choice do we have?
It's not home, but
it'll do just fine.
What a lovely bed.
- Got ya.
- I found some cheese.
Awful stuff.
- Is that you, Gorder?
- How did you know?
Enough! What are you
doing in my house?
Hey!
Oh, no, no, no.
Dead broad off the table.
Where are we supposed to put her?
The bed's taken.
What?
I live in a swamp. I put up signs.
I'm a terrifying ogre!
What do I have to do to
get a little privacy?
Oh, no.
No! No!
What?
- Quit it.
- Don't push.
What are you doing
in my swamp?
Oh, dear!
All right, get out of here.
All of you, move it!
Come on! Let's go! Hapaya!
Hapaya! Hey!
- Quickly. Come on!
- No, no!
No, no. Not there. Not there.
Hey, don't look at me.
I didn't invite them.
Oh, gosh, no one invited us.
- What?
- We were forced to come here.
- By who?
- Lord Farquaad.
He huffed und he puffed und he
signed an eviction notice.
All right.
Who knows where this
Farquaad guy is?
Oh, I do. I know where he is.
Does anyone else know
where to find him?
- Any one at all?
- Me! Me!
- Anyone?
- Oh, pick me!
Oh, I know! I know! Me, me!
Okay, fine.
Attention, all
fairy tale things.
Do not get comfortable. Your
welcome is officially worn out.
In fact, I'm gonna see this
guy Farquaad right now...
and get you all off my land
and back where you came from!
Oh! You!
You're coming with me.
All right, that's what
I like to hear, man.
Shrek and Donkey, two stalwart friends,
off on a whirlwind big-city adventure.
I love it!
On the road again...
Sing it with me, Shrek.
I can't wait to get
on the road again.
What did I say about singing?
- Can I whistle?
- No.
- Can I hum it?
- All right, hum it.
That's enough.
He's ready to talk.
Run, run, run, as
fast as you can.
You can't catch me.
I'm the gingerbread man!
- You're a monster.
- I'm not the monster here. You are.
You and the rest of that fairy tale
trash, poisoning my perfect world.
Now, tell me!
Where are the others?
Eat me!
I've tried to be fair
to you creatures.
Now my patience has reached
its end! Tell me or I'll...
No, no, not the buttons.
Not my gumdrop buttons.
All right then.
Who's hiding them?
Okay, I'll tell you.
Do you know the muffin man?
- The muffin man?
- The muffin man.
Yes, I know the muffin man,
who lives on Drury Lane?
Well, she's married
to the muffin man.
- The muffin man?
- The muffin man!
She's married to the muffin man.
My Lord! We found it.
Then what are you waiting for?
Bring it in.
- Magic mirror...
- Don't tell him anything!
No!
Evening.
Mirror, mirror, on the wall.
Is this not the most perfect
kingdom of them all?
Well, technically
you're not a king.
Thelonius.
- You were saying?
- What I mean is, you're not a king yet.
But you can become one. All you
have to do is marry a princess.
Go on.
So, just sit back
and relax, my Lord,
because it's time for you to meet
today's eligible bachelorettes.
And here they are!
Bachelorette number one is a mentally
abused shut-in from a kingdom far, faraway.
She likes Sushi and
hot tubbing anytime.
Her hobbies include cooking and
cleaning for her two evil sisters.
Please welcome Cinderella.
Bachelorette number two is a cape-wearing
girl from the land of fancy.
Although she lives with seven
other men, she's not easy.
Just kiss her dead, frozen lips and
find out what a live wire she is.
Come on. Give it
up for Snow White!
And last, but
certainly not least,
bachelorette number three
is a fiery redhead...
from a dragon-guarded castle
surrounded by hot boiling lava!
But don't let that cool you off.
She's a loaded pistol who likes pina
coladas and getting caught in the rain.
Yours for the rescuing,
Princess Fiona!
So will it be
bachelorette number one,
bachelorette number two or
bachelorette number three?
- Two! Two!
- Three! Three!
- Three!
Three? One? Three?
Three! Pick number
three, my Lord!
Okay, okay, number three!
Lord Farquaad, you've
chosen Princess Fiona.
If you love pina coladas
- And getting caught in the rain
- Princess Fiona.
- If you're not into yoga
- She's perfect.
All I have to do is just
find someone who can go...
But I probably should mention the
little thing that happens at night.
- I'll do it.
- Yes, but after sunset...
Silence! I will make this
Princess Fiona my queen,
and DuLoc will finally
have the perfect king!
Captain, assemble
your finest men.
We're going to
have a tournament.
But that's it. That's it right there.
That's DuLoc.
I told ya I'd find it.
So, that must be Lord
Farquaad's castle.
That's the place.
Do you think maybe he's
compensating for something?
Hey, wait. Wait up, Shrek.
Hurry, darling. We're late.
Hurry.
Hey, you!
Wait a second. Look,
I'm not gonna eat ya.
I just... I just...
It's quiet.
Too quiet.
- Where is everybody?
- Hey, look at this!
Welcome to DuLoc
such a perfect town
Here we have some rules,
let us lay them down
Don't make waves, stay in line
and we'll get along fine
DuLoc is a perfect place
Please keep off of the grass,
shine your shoes, wipe your face
DuLoc is, DuLoc is...
DuLoc is a perfect place
Wow! Let's do that again!
No. No. No, no, no! No.
Brave knights.
You are the best and
brightest in all the land.
Today one of you shall
prove himself...
All right. You're going the
right way for a smacked bottom.
Sorry about that.
That champion shall have the honour,
no, no, the privilege...
to go forth and rescue the
lovely Princess Fiona...
from the fiery keep
of the dragon.
If for any reason the
winner is unsuccessful,
the first runner-up
will take his place...
and so on and so forth.
Some of you may die, but it's a
sacrifice I am willing to make.
Let the tournament begin!
What is that?
- It's hideous!
- That's not very nice.
It's just a donkey.
Indeed. Knights, new plan!
The one who kills the ogre will
be named champion! Have at him!
- Get him!
- Oh, hey! Now come on! Hang on now.
Go ahead! Get him!
Can't we just settle
this over a pint?
Kill the beast!
No? All right then.
Come on!
I don't give a damn
about my reputation
You're living in the past,
it's a new generation
A girl can do what
she wants to do
And that's what I'm gonna do
And I don't give a damn
about my bad reputation
Oh, no, no, no, no, no,
not me
Hey, Shrek, tag me! Tag me!
And I don't give a damn
about my reputation
Never said I wanted to
improve my station
And I'm always feeling good
when I'm having fun
And I don't have
to please no one
The chair! Give him the chair!
And I don't give a damn
about my bad reputation
Oh, no, no, no, no, no,
not me
Oh, no, no, no, no
Not me, not me
Not me
Oh, yeah!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
I'm here till Thursday.
Try the veal!
Shall I give the order, sir?
No, I have a better idea.
People of DuLoc,
I give you our champion!
- What?
- Congratulations, ogre.
You've won the honour of embarking
on a great and noble quest.
Quest? I'm already on a quest,
a quest to get my swamp back.
- Your swamp?
- Yeah, my swamp!
Where you dumped those
fairy tale creatures!
Indeed.
All right, ogre,
I'll make you a deal.
Go on this quest for me, and
I'll give you your swamp back.
Exactly the way it was?
Down to the last
slime-covered toad stool.
- And the squatters?
- As good as gone.
What kind of quest?
Let me get this straight.
You're gonna go fight a dragon...
and rescue a princess just so Farquaad
will give you back a swamp...
which you only don't have because he filled
it full of freaks in the first place.
Is that about right?
Maybe there's a good reason
donkeys shouldn't talk.
I don't get it. Why don't you just
pull some of that ogre stuff on him?
Throttle him, lay siege
to his fortress,
grind his bones to make your
bread, the whole ogre trip.
Oh, I know what.
Maybe I could have decapitated
an entire village...
and put their heads on a pike,
gotten a knife, cut open their
spleen and drink their fluids.
Does that sound good to you?
No, not really, no.
For your information, there's a lot
more to ogres than people think.
- Example?
- Okay, ogres are like onions.
- They stink?
- Yes... No! No!
- They make you cry?
You leave them out in the sun, they get all
brown, start sprouting little white hairs.
No! Layers!
Onions have layers.
Ogres have layers!
You get it? We both have layers.
Oh, you both have layers.
You know, not everybody likes onions.
Cake! Everybody loves cakes!
Cakes have layers.
I don't care what
everyone likes.
Ogres are not like cakes.
You know what else everybody
likes? Parfaits.
Have you ever met a person, you
say, let's get some parfait,
they say, no, I don't
like no parfait?
- Parfaits are delicious.
- No!
You dense, irritating,
miniature beast of burden!
Ogres are like onions!
End of story. Bye-bye.
See ya later.
Parfaits may be the most delicious
thing on the whole damn planet.
You know, I think
I preferred your humming.
Do you have a tissue or something?
I'm making a mess.
Just the word parfait
make me start slobbering.
I'm on my way from misery
to happiness today
And everything that you
receive up yonder
Is what you give to
me the day I wander
I'm on my way
Ooh! Shrek! Did you do that?
You gotta warn somebody before you
just crack one off. My mouth was open.
Believe me, Donkey, if it
was me, you'd be dead.
It's brimstone.
- We must be getting close.
- Yeah, right, brimstone.
Don't be talking about
it's the brimstone.
I know what I smell.
It wasn't no brimstone.
It didn't come off no stone neither.
Sure, it's big enough, but
look at the location.
Shrek? Remember when
you said ogres have layers?
Oh, aye.
Well, I have a bit of
a confession to make.
Donkeys don't have layers. We wear our
fear right out there on our sleeves.
Wait a second. Donkeys
don't have sleeves.
You know what I mean.
You can't tell me you're
afraid of heights.
I'm just a little uncomfortable
about being on
a rickety bridge over a
boiling lake of lava!
Come on, Donkey. I'm right
here beside ya, okay?
For emotional support,
we'll just tackle this thing together
one little baby step at a time.
- Really?
- Really, really.
- Okay, that makes me feel so much better.
- Just keep moving.
- And don't look down.
- Okay, don't look down. Don't look down.
Don't look down. Keep on moving.
Don't look down.
Shrek! I'm looking down!
Oh, God, I can't do this!
Just let me off, please!
- But you're already halfway.
- But I know that half is safe!
Okay, fine. I don't have time for this.
You go back.
- Shrek, no! Wait!
- Just, Donkey...
- Let's have a dance then, shall we?
- Don't do that!
Oh, I'm sorry. Do what?
- Oh, this?
- Yes, that!
Yes? Yes, do it. Okay.
No, Shrek!
- No! Stop it!
- You said do it! I'm doing it.
I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die.
Shrek, I'm gonna die.
That'll do, Donkey.
That'll do.
Cool.
So where is this fire-breathing
pain-in-the-neck anyway?
Inside, waiting for
us to rescue her.
I was talking about
the dragon, Shrek.
You afraid?
No, but...
Oh, good. Me neither.
'Cause there's nothing
wrong with being afraid.
Fear's a sensible response
to an unfamiliar situation.
Unfamiliar dangerous
situation, I might add.
With a dragon that breathes fire and
eats knights and breathes fire,
it sure doesn't mean you're a
coward if you're a little scared.
I sure as heck am not a coward.
I know that.
Donkey, two things, okay?
Shut up.
Now go over there and see
if you can find any stairs.
Stairs? I thought we was
looking for the princess.
The princess will be up the stairs in
the highest room in the tallest tower.
- What makes you think she'll be there?
- I read it in a book once.
Cool. You handle the dragon.
I'll handle the stairs.
I'll find those stairs.
I'll whip their butt too.
Those stairs won't know
which way they're going.
I'm gonna take drastic steps.
Kick it to the kerb. Don't mess with me.
I'm the stair master.
I've mastered the stairs. I wish I had a
step right here. I'd step all over it.
Well, at least we know where the
princess is, but where's the...
Dragon!
Donkey, look out!
Got ya!
No. Oh, no. No!
Oh, what large teeth you have.
I mean, white, sparkling teeth.
I know you
probably hear this all
the time from your food,
but you must bleach, 'cause that is
one dazzling smile you got there.
Do I detect a hint
of minty freshness?
And you know what else? You're...
You're a girl dragon!
Oh, sure! I mean, of course
you're a girl dragon.
You're just reeking
of feminine beauty.
What's the matter with you?
You got something in your eye?
Man, I'd really love to stay,
but, you know, I'm...
I'm an asthmatic, and I don't know if it'd
work out if you're gonna blow smoke rings.
Shrek!
No! Shrek! Shrek!
- Wake up!
- What?
Are you Princess Fiona?
I am, awaiting a knight
so bold as to rescue me.
Oh, that's nice. Now let's go!
But wait, Sir Knight.
This be-ith our first meeting.
Should it not be a wonderful,
romantic moment?
- Yeah, sorry, lady. There's no time.
- Hey, wait. What are you doing?
You should sweep me
off my feet...
out yonder window and down a
rope on to your valiant steed.
You've had a lot of time
to plan this, haven't you?
But we have to
savour this moment!
You could recite an
epic poem for me.
A ballad? A sonnet!
- A limerick? Or something!
- I don't think so.
Can I at least know the
name of my champion?
Shrek.
Sir Shrek.
I pray that you take this favour
as a token of my gratitude.
Thanks!
You didn't slay the dragon?
It's on my to-do list.
Now come on!
But this isn't right!
You were meant to charge in,
sword drawn, banner flying.
That's what all the
other knights did.
Yeah, right before
they burst into flame.
That's not the point.
Wait. Where are you going?
The exit's over there.
Well, I have to save my ass.
What kind of knight are you?
One of a kind.
Slowdown. Slowdown, baby, please.
I believe it's healthy to get to know
someone over a long period of time.
Just call me old-fashioned.
I don't want to rush into
a physical relationship.
I'm not emotionally ready for
a commitment of this...
Magnitude really is the
word I'm looking for.
Magnitude... Hey, that is
unwanted physical contact.
Hey, what are you doing?
Okay, okay. Let's just backup a little
and take this one step at a time.
We really should get to know each
other first as friends or pen pals.
I'm on the road a lot,
but I just love receiving cards...
I'd really love to stay, but...
Don't do that! That's my tail!
That's my personal tail.
You're gonna tear it off.
I don't give permission...
What are you gonna do
with that?
Hey, now. No way. No! No!
No, no! No. No, no, no!
No! Oh!
- Hi, Princess!
- It talks!
Yeah, it's getting him to
shut up that's the trick.
Okay, you two,
head for the exit!
I'll take care of the dragon.
Run!
You did it!
You rescued me! You're amazing.
You're...
You're wonderful. You're...
a little unorthodox I'll admit.
But thy deed is great,
and thine heart is pure.
I am eternally in your debt.
And where would a brave knight
be without his noble steed?
I hope you heard that.
She called me a noble steed.
She think I'm a steed.
The battle is won.
You may remove your helmet,
good Sir Knight.
- No.
- Why not?
I have helmet hair.
Please. I would'st look upon
the face of my rescuer.
No, no, you wouldn't... 'st.
But how will you kiss me?
What? That wasn't in
the job description.
Maybe it's a perk.
No, it's destiny. Oh, you
must know how it goes.
A princess locked in a tower
and beset by a dragon...
is rescued by a brave knight,
and then they share
true love's first kiss.
With Shrek? You think...
Wait.
Wait. You think that
Shrek is your true love?
Well, yes.
You think Shrek is
your true love!
What is so funny?
Let's just say
I'm not your type, okay?
Of course, you are.
You're my rescuer.
Now...
Now remove your helmet.
Look. I really don't think
this is a good idea.
- Just take off the helmet.
- I'm not going to.
- Take it off.
- No!
- Now!
- Okay!
Easy. As you command,
Your Highness.
You... You're an ogre.
Oh, you were expecting
Prince Charming.
Well, yes, actually.
Oh, no. This is all wrong.
You're not supposed
to be an ogre.
Princess, I was sent to
rescue you by Lord Farquaad, okay?
He's the one who
wants to marry you.
Then why didn't he
come rescue me?
Good question. You should ask
him that when we get there.
But I have to be rescued
by my true love,
not by some ogre and
his pet.
So much for noble steed.
You're not making
my job any easier.
I'm sorry, but your job
is not my problem.
You can tell Lord Farquaad that if
he wants to rescue me properly,
I'll be waiting for
him right here.
Hey! I'm no one's messenger boy,
all right? I'm a delivery boy.
You wouldn't dare.
- Ya coming, Donkey?
- Put me down!
I'm right behind ya.
Put me down, or you will
suffer the consequences!
This is not dignified!
Put me down!
Okay, so here's
another question.
Say there's a woman that digs you, right,
but you don't really like her that way.
How do you let her down real easy
so her feelings aren't hurt,
but you don't get burned
to a crisp and eaten?
You just tell her she's
not your true love.
Everyone knowest what happens
when you find your...
Hey!
The sooner we get to
DuLoc the better.
You're gonna love it there, Princess.
It's beautiful!
And what of my groom-to-be?
Lord Farquaad? What's he like?
Let me put it this
way, Princess.
Men of Farquaad's stature
are in short supply.
I don't know. There are those
who think little of him.
Stop it. Stop it, both of you.
You're just jealous you can never measure
up to a great ruler like Lord Farquaad.
Yeah, well, maybe
you're right, Princess.
But I'll let you do the measuring
when you see him tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
It'll take that long?
- Shouldn't we stop to make camp?
- No, that'll take longer.
- We can keep going.
- But there's robbers in the woods.
Time out, Shrek!
Camping is starting to sound good.
Hey, come on. I'm scarier than anything
we're going to see in this forest.
I need to find
somewhere to camp now!
- Hey! Over here.
- Shrek, we can do better than that.
I don't think this is
fit for a princess.
No, no, it's perfect. It just
needs a few homey touches.
Homey touches? Like what?
A door? Well, gentlemen,
I bid thee good night.
You want me to read you a
bedtime story? I will.
I said good night!
Shrek, what are you doing?
I just... You know...
Oh, come on.
I was just kidding.
And that one,
that's Throwback,
the only ogre to ever spit
over three wheat fields.
Right. Yeah.
Hey, can you tell my future
from these stars?
The stars don't tell the future,
Donkey. They tell stories.
Look there's
Bloodnut the Flatulent.
- You can guess what he's famous for.
- I know you're making this up.
No, look. There he is,
and there's the group of hunters
running away from his stench.
That is nothing but a
bunch of little dots.
Sometimes things are
more than they appear.
Forget it.
Hey, Shrek, what we gonna do
when we get our swamp anyway?
Our swamp?
You know, when we're through
rescuing the princess.
We? Donkey, there's no we.
There's no our.
There's just me and my swamp.
The first thing I'm gonna do is build
a ten-foot wall around my land.
You cut me deep, Shrek.
You cut me real deep just now.
You know what I think?
I think this whole wall thing is
just a way to keep somebody out.
- No, do ya think?
- Are you hiding something?
Never mind, Donkey.
Oh, this is another one of
those onion things, isn't it?
No, this is one of those drop-it
and leave-it-alone things.
- Why don't you want to talk about it?
- Why do you want to?
- Why are you blocking?
- I'm not blocking.
- Oh, yes, you are.
- Donkey, I'm warning you.
- Who you trying to keep out?
- Everyone! Okay?
Oh, now we're getting somewhere.
Oh! For the love of Pete!
What's your problem? What you
got against the whole world?
I'm not the one with
the problem, okay?
It's the world that seems
to have a problem with me.
People take one look at me
and go, aah! Help! Run!
A big, stupid, ugly ogre!
They judge me
before they even know me.
That's why I'm better off alone.
You know what?
When we met, I didn't think you was
just a big, stupid, ugly ogre.
Yeah, I know.
So, are there any
donkeys up there?
Well, there's Gabby,
the Small and Annoying.
Okay, I see it now. The big shiny
one, right there. That one there?
- That's the moon.
- Oh, okay.
Again. Show me again.
Mirror, mirror, show her to me.
Show me the princess.
Perfect.
Mmm, yeah, you know
I like it like that.
- Come on, baby. I said I like it.
- Donkey, wake up.
- Huh? What?
- Wake up.
- What?
- Good morning.
How do you like your eggs?
- Good morning, Princess!
- What's all this about?
We kind of got off to a
bad start yesterday.
I wanted to make it up to you.
After all, you did rescue me.
Thanks.
Well, eat up. We've got
a big day ahead of us.
Shrek!
What? It's a compliment.
Better out than in,
I always say.
Well, it's no way to behave in
front of a princess.
- Thanks.
- She's as nasty as you are.
You know, you're not
exactly what I expected.
Maybe you shouldn't judge people
before you get to know them.
La Libert! Hey!
Princess!
What are you doing?
Be still, Mon Chrie,
for I am your saviour!
And I am rescuing you
from this green...
- Beast.
- Hey!
That's my princess!
Go find your own!
Please, monster! Can't you
see I'm a little busy here?
Look, pal, I don't know
who you think you are!
Oh! Of course! Oh, how rude.
Please let me
introduce myself.
Oh, Merry Men!
I steal from the rich
and give to the needy
- He takes a wee percentage
- But I'm not greedy
I rescue pretty damsels,
man, I'm good
- What a guy, Monsieur Hood
- Break it down
I like an honest fight
and a saucy little maid
What he's basically saying is
he likes to get paid
When an ogre in the bush
grabs a lady by the tush
- That's bad
When a beauty's with a beast,
it makes me awfully mad
He's mad, he's really,
really mad
I'll take my blade and ram
it through your heart
Keep your eyes on me, boys,
'cause I'm about to start
Man, that was annoying!
Oh, you little...
Shall we?
Hold the phone.
Hold on now.
- Where did that come from?
- What?
That! Back there.
That was amazing!
Where did you learn that?
Well, when one lives alone,
one has to learn these things
in case there's a...
- There's an arrow in your butt!
- What?
- Oh, would you look at that?
- Oh, no. This is all my fault.
- I'm so sorry.
- Why? What's wrong?
- Shrek's hurt.
Shrek's hurt?
Oh, no, Shrek's gonna die.
Donkey, I'm okay.
You can't do this to me.
I'm too young for you to die.
Keep your legs elevated.
Turn your head and cough.
- Does anyone know the Heimlich?
- Donkey! Calm down.
If you want to help Shrek,
run into the woods
and find me a blue flower
with red thorns.
Blue flower, red thorns. Okay, I'm on it.
Blue flower, red thorns.
Don't die, Shrek. If you see a long
tunnel, stay away from the light!
- Donkey!
- Oh, yeah. Right. Blue flower, red thorns.
- Blue flower, red thorns.
- What are the flowers for?
For getting rid of Donkey.
Now you hold still, and
I'll yank this thing out.
Ow! Hey! Easy
with the yanking.
- I'm sorry, but it has to come out.
- No, it's tender.
Now, hold on.
What you're doing is
the opposite of help.
Don't move.
- Look, time out.
- Would you...
Okay.
What do you propose we do?
Blue flower, red thorns.
This would be so much easier
if I wasn't colour-blind!
Blue flower, red thorns.
Hold on, Shrek! I'm coming!
Not good.
Okay. Okay, I can nearly
see the head.
It's just about...
Nothing happened.
We were just...
Look, if you wanted to be alone,
all you had to do was ask.
Oh, come on! That's the
last thing on my mind.
The princess here
was just...
Hey, what's that?
That's... Is that blood?
My beloved monster and me
We go everywhere together
Wearing a raincoat
that has four sleeves
Gets us through
all kinds of weather
She will always be
the only thing
That comes between me
and the awful sting
That comes from living in a
world that's so damn mean
Hey!
There it is, Princess.
Your future awaits you.
- That's DuLoc?
- Yeah, I know.
You know, Shrek thinks Lord Farquaad's
compensating for something,
which I think means
he has a really...
I...
- I guess we better move on.
- Sure.
But, Shrek?
I'm...
I'm worried about Donkey.
- What?
- I mean, look at him.
- He doesn't look so good.
- What are you talking about? I'm fine.
That's what they always say, and then
next thing you know, you're on your back.
- Dead.
- You know, she's right.
You look awful. Do you
want to sit down?
- I'll make you some tea.
- I didn't want to say nothing,
but I got this twinge in my neck, and
when I turn my head like this, look.
Ow! See?
- Who's hungry? I'll find us some dinner.
- I'll get the firewood.
Hey, where you going?
Oh, man, I can't feel my toes!
I don't have any toes!
I think I need a hug.
This is good.
This is really good.
- What is this?
- Weedrat.
Rotisserie style.
No kidding.
Well, this is delicious.
Well, they're also
great in stews.
Now, I don't mean to brag, but
I make a mean weedrat stew.
I guess I'll be dining a little
differently tomorrow night.
Maybe you can come visit me
in the swamp sometime.
I'll cook all kinds
of stuff for you.
Swamp toad soup, fish eye tartar,
you name it.
I'd like that.
See the pyramids along
the Nile
- Princess?
- Yes, Shrek?
I was wondering.
Are you...
You belong to me
Are you gonna eat that?
Man, isn't this romantic?
Just look at that sunset.
Sunset? Oh, no!
I mean, it's late.
- It's very late.
- What?
Wait a minute. I see
what's going on here.
- You're afraid of the dark, aren't you?
- Yes!
Yes, that's it. I'm terrified.
You know, I'd better go inside.
Don't feel bad, Princess. I used to
be afraid of the dark too, until...
Hey, no, wait. I'm still
afraid of the dark.
Good night.
Now I really see
what's going on here.
Oh, what are you
talking about?
I don't even wanna hear it. Look,
I'm an animal, and I got instincts.
I know you two were digging on
each other. I could feel it.
You're crazy. I'm just bringing
her back to Farquaad.
Oh, come on, Shrek. Wake up
and smell the pheromones.
Just go on in and tell her
how you feel.
There's nothing to tell. Besides,
even if I did tell her that,
well, you know...
and I'm not saying I do
'cause I don't...
She's a princess, and I'm...
An ogre?
Yeah. An ogre.
- Hey, where you going?
- To get more firewood.
Princess?
Princess Fiona?
Princess, where are you?
Princess?
It's very spooky in here.
I am not playing no games.
Oh, no! No, help!
- Shrek! Shrek! Shrek!
- No, it's okay. It's okay.
- What did you do with the princess?
- Donkey, I'm the princess.
It's me, in this body.
Oh, my God!
You ate the princess!
- Can you hear me?
- Donkey!
Listen, keep breathing!
I'll get you out of there!
Shrek! Shrek! Shrek!
- Shrek!
- This is me.
Princess?
What happened to you?
You're...
different.
- I'm ugly, okay?
- Well, yeah!
Was it something you ate? 'Cause I
told Shrek those rats was a bad idea.
- You are what you eat, I said. Now...
- No.
I've been this way
as long as I can remember.
What do you mean? Look, I have
never seen you like this before.
It only happens when
the sun goes down.
By night one way,
by day another.
This shall be the norm...
until you find true
love's first kiss...
and then take
love's true form.
Ah, that's beautiful.
I didn't know you wrote poetry.
It's a spell.
When I was a little girl,
a witch cast a spell on me.
Every night I become this.
This horrible, ugly beast!
I was placed in a tower to await the
day my true love would rescue me.
That's why I have to marry
Lord Farquaad tomorrow...
before the sun sets
and he sees me...
like this.
All right, all right. Calm down.
Look, it's not that bad.
You're not that ugly.
Well, I am not gonna lie. You are ugly.
But you only look like this at night.
Shrek's ugly 24-7.
But, Donkey, I'm a princess,
and this is not how a
princess is meant to look.
Princess, how about if you
don't marry Farquaad?
I have to.
Only my true love's kiss
can break the spell.
But, you know,
you're kind of an ogre,
and Shrek, well,
you got a lot in common.
Shrek?
Princess, I...
How's it going, first of all?
Good? Good for me too.
I'm okay.
I saw this flower and thought of
you because it's pretty and...
well, I don't really like it, but I thought
you might like it 'cause you're pretty.
But I like you anyway.
I'd...
I'm in trouble.
Okay, here we go.
I can't just marry
whoever I want.
Take a good look
at me, Donkey.
I mean, really,
who could ever love a beast
so hideous and ugly?
Princess and ugly
don't go together.
That's why I can't stay
here with Shrek.
My only chance to live happily ever
after is to marry my truelove.
Don't you see, Donkey?
That's just how it has to be.
It's the only way
to break the spell.
- You at least gotta tell Shrek the truth.
- No!
You can't breathe a word.
No one must ever know.
What's the point of being able to
talk if you gotta keep secrets?
Promise you won't tell.
Promise!
All right, all right. I won't tell him.
But you should.
I just know before this is over, I'm gonna
need a whole lot of serious therapy.
Look at my eye twitching.
I tell him, I tell him not.
I tell him.
Shrek!
Shrek, there's
something I want...
Shrek.
- Are you all right?
- Perfect!
Never been better.
I... I don't... There's
something I have to tell you.
You don't have to tell
me anything, Princess.
- I heard enough last night.
- You heard what I said?
Every word.
I thought you'd understand.
Oh, I understand.
Like you said, who could
love a hideous, ugly beast?
But I thought that
wouldn't matter to you.
Yeah? Well, it does.
Ah, right on time.
Princess, I've brought
you a little something.
What'd I miss? What'd I miss?
Who said that?
Couldn't have been a donkey.
Princess Fiona.
As promised. Now hand it over.
Very well, ogre. The deed to your
swamp, cleared out, as agreed.
Take it and go before
I change my mind.
Forgive me, Princess,
for startling you,
but you startled me,
for I have never seen such
a radiant beauty before.
I am Lord Farquaad.
Lord Farquaad?
Oh, no, no.
Forgive me, my Lord, for
I was just saying...
a short farewell.
That is so sweet. You don't have
to waste good manners on the ogre.
It's not like it has feelings.
No, you're right. It doesn't.
Princess Fiona, beautiful,
fair, flawless Fiona.
I ask your hand in marriage.
Will you be the perfect bride
for the perfect groom?
Lord Farquaad, I accept.
Nothing would make...
Excellent! I'll start the
plans, for tomorrow we wed!
No! I mean...
Why wait?
Let's get married today
before the sun sets.
Oh, anxious, are we?
You're right.
The sooner, the better.
There's so much to do!
There's the caterer, the cake,
the band, the guest list.
Captain, round up some guests!
Fare-thee-well, ogre.
Shrek, what are you doing?
You're letting her get away.
Yeah? So what?
Shrek, there's something
about her you don't know.
Look, I talked to her last night.
She's...
I know you talked to her last night.
You're great pals, aren't ya?
Now, if you two are such good friends,
why don't you follow her home?
Shrek, I wanna go with you.
I told you, didn't I? You're
not coming home with me.
I live alone! My swamp!
Me! Nobody else!
Understand? Nobody!
Especially useless, pathetic,
annoying, talking donkeys!
- But I thought...
- Yeah. You know what?
You thought wrong!
Shrek.
I heard there was
a secret chord
That David played and
it pleased the Lord
But you don't really
care for music, do ya
It goes like this the fourth,
the fifth
The minor fall,
the major lift
The baffled king
composing hallelujah
Hallelujah.
Hallelujah
Baby, I've been here before
I know this room,
I've walked this floor
I used to live alone
before I knew you
I've seen your flag
on the marble arch
But love is not a
victory march.
It's a cold and it's
a broken hallelujah
Hallelujah
And all I ever
learned from love
Is how to shoot
at someone
Who outdrew you
And it's not a cry
you can hear at night
It's not somebody
who's seen the light
It's a cold and it's
a broken hallelujah
Hallelujah
Donkey?
What are you doing?
I would think, of all people, you would
recognise a wall when you see one.
Well, yeah.
But the wall's supposed to go
around my swamp, not through it.
It is around your half. See, that's
your half, and this is my half.
Oh! Your half.
Yes, my half. I helped
rescue the princess.
I did half the work,
I get half the booty.
Now hand me that big old rock,
the one that looks like your head.
- Back off!
- No, you back off.
- This is my swamp!
- Our swamp.
- Let go, Donkey!
- You let go.
- Stubborn jackass!
- Smelly ogre.
Fine!
Hey, come back here.
I'm not through with you yet.
Well, I'm through with you.
You know, with you,
it's always me, me, me!
Well, guess what!
Now it's my turn!
So you just shut up
and pay attention!
You are mean to me.
You insult me and you don't
appreciate anything that I do!
You're always pushing me
around or pushing me away.
Oh, yeah? Well, if I treated you
so bad, how come you came back?
Because that's what friends do!
They forgive each other!
Oh, yeah.
You're right, Donkey.
I forgive you for
stabbing me in the back!
You're so wrapped up in layers, onion boy,
you're afraid of your own feelings.
Go away!
There you are, doing it
again just like you did to Fiona.
All she ever do was like,
maybe even love you.
Love me? She said I was ugly,
a hideous creature.
I heard the two of you talking.
She wasn't talking about you.
She was talking about
somebody else.
She wasn't talking about me?
Well, then who was
she talking about?
No way. I am not saying anything.
You don't wanna listen to me.
- Right? Right?
- Donkey!
- No!
- Okay, look.
I'm sorry, all right?
I'm sorry.
I guess I am just a big,
stupid, ugly ogre.
Can you forgive me?
Hey, that's what friends
are for, right?
Right. Friends?
Friends.
So...
what did Fiona say about me?
What are you asking me for?
Why don't you just go ask her?
The wedding! We'll
never make it in time.
Never fear, for where
there's a will, there's a way,
and I have a way.
Donkey?
I guess it's just
my animal magnetism.
Aw, come here, you.
All right, all right.
Don't get all slobbery.
No one likes a kiss ass.
All right, hop on
and hold on tight.
I haven't had a chance to
install the seat belts yet.
People of DuLoc,
we gather here today...
to bear witness...
to the union...
- of our new king...
- Excuse me.
Could we just skip ahead
to the I do's?
Go on.
Go ahead, have some fun. If we need
you, I'll whistle. How about that?
Shrek, wait, wait!
Wait a minute!
- You wanna do this right, don't you?
- What are you talking about?
There's a line you
gotta wait for.
The preacher's gonna say, speak
now or forever hold your peace.
- That's when you say, I object!
- I don't have time for this!
Wait. What are you doing?
Listen to me!
- Look, you love this woman, don't you?
- Yes.
- You wanna hold her?
- Please her?
- Yes!
Then you got to, got to
try a little tenderness.
- The chicks love that romantic crap!
- All right! Cut it out.
- When does this guy say the line?
- We gotta check it out.
And so, by the power
vested in me...
- What do you see?
- The whole town's in there.
- I now pronounce you husband and wife.
- They're at the altar.
- King and queen.
- Mother Fletcher! He already said it.
Oh, for the love of Pete!
I object!
Shrek?
Oh, now what does he want?
Hi, everyone. Having
a good time, are ya?
I love DuLoc, first of all.
- Very clean.
- What are you doing here?
Really, it's rude enough being
alive when no one wants you.
- But showing up uninvited to a wedding...
- Fiona!
- I need to talk to you.
- Oh, now you wanna talk?
It's a little late for that,
so if you'll excuse me...
- But you can't marry him.
- And why not?
Because... Because he's just
marrying you so he can be king.
Outrageous! Fiona,
don't listen to him.
- He's not your true love.
- And what do you know about true love?
Well, I...
- I mean...
- Oh, this is precious.
The ogre has fallen
in love with the princess!
Oh, good Lord.
An ogre and a princess!
Shrek, is this true?
Who cares? It's preposterous!
Fiona, my love, we're but a kiss
away from our happily ever after.
Now kiss me!
By night one way,
by day another.
I wanted to show you before.
Well...
that explains a lot.
It's disgusting!
Guards! Guards!
I order you to get that out
of my sight now! Get them!
- Get them both!
- No, no!
This hocus-pocus alters nothing.
This marriage is binding,
and that makes me king!
- See? See?
- No, let go of me! Shrek!
- No!
- Don't just stand there, you morons.
Get out of my way!
Fiona!
I'll make you regret the day we met.
I'll see you drawn and quartered!
- You'll beg for death to save you!
- No! Shrek!
- And as for you, my wife...
- Fiona!
I'll have you locked back in that
tower for the rest of your days!
I am king!
I will have order! I will have
perfection! I will have...
All right. Nobody move.
I got a dragon here, and
I'm not afraid to use it.
I'm a donkey on the edge!
Celebrity marriages.
They never last, do they?
Go ahead, Shrek.
Fiona?
Yes, Shrek?
I... I love you.
Really?
Really, really.
I love you too.
Until you find truelove's
first kiss...
and then take love's
true form.
Take love's true form.
Fiona?
Fiona.
Are you all right?
Well, yes.
But I don't understand.
I'm supposed to be beautiful.
But you are beautiful.
I was hoping this would
be a happy ending.
I thought love was only
true in fairy tales
Meant for someone
else but not for me
Love was out to get me
That's the way it seemed
Disappointment haunted
all my dreams
And then I saw her face
Now I'm a believer
And not a trace
Of doubt in my mind
I'm in love
I'm a believer,
I couldn't leave her
If I tried
God bless us, every one.
Come on, y'all!
Then I saw her face!
Now I'm a believer!
Listen!
Not a trace
Of doubt in my mind
I'm in love
I'm a believer I couldn't
leave her if I tried
Then I saw her face
Now I'm a believer!
Hey!
Not a trace
Of doubt in my mind!
One more time!
I'm in love
I'm a believer
Come on!
I believe, I believe
I believe, I believe I believe,
I believe, I believe, hey
Y'all sing it with me!
I...
Believe
I believe!
People in the back!
I'm a believer!
I believe
Oh, that's funny.
I can't breathe.