Once upon a time there
was a lovely princess.
But she had an enchantment
upon her of a fearful sort...
which could only be broken
by love's first kiss.
She was locked away
in a castle...
guarded by a terrible
fire-breathing dragon.
Many brave knights had attempted to
free her from this dreadful prison,
but none prevailed.
She waited in the dragon's
keep...
in the highest room of
the tallest tower...
for her true love and
true love's first kiss.
Like that's ever gonna happen.
What a load of...
Somebody once told me the
world is gonna roll me
I am not the sharpest
tool in the shed
She was looking kind of dumb
with her finger and her thumb
In the shape of an L
on her forehead
The years start coming and
they don't stop coming
Fed to the rules and
I hit the ground running
Didn't make sense not
to live for fun
Your brain gets smart but
your head gets dumb
So much to do, so much to see
So what's wrong with
taking the backstreets
You'll never know
if you don't go
You'll never shine
if you don't glow
Hey, now, you're an all-star
Get your game on, go play
Hey, now, you're a rock star,
get the show on, get paid
And all that glitters is gold
Only shooting stars
break the mould
It's a cool place and
they say it gets colder
You're bundled up now but
wait till you get older
But the meteor men
beg to differ
Judging by the hole in
the satellite picture
The ice we skate is
getting pretty thin
The water's getting warm
so you might as well swim
My world's on fire,
how about yours
That's the way I like it
and I'll never get bored
Hey, now, you're an all-star
Get your game on, go play
Hey, now, you're a rock star,
get the show on, get paid
And all that glitters is gold
Only shooting stars
break the mould
- Go!
Go. Go. Go.
Hey, now, you're an all-star
Get your game on, go play
Hey, now, you're a rock star,
get the show on, get paid
And all that glitters is gold
Only shooting stars
break the mould
- Think it's in there?
- All right. Let's get it!
Whoa. Hold on. Do you know
what that thing can do to you?
Yeah, it'll grind your
bones for its bread.
Yes, well, actually,
that would be a giant.
Now, ogres...
they're much worse.
They'll make a suit from
your freshly peeled skin.
- No!
- They'll shave your liver.
Squeeze the jelly
from your eyes!
- Actually, it's quite good on toast.
- Back! Back, beast!
Back! I warn ya!
Right.
This is the part where
you run away.
And stay out!
Wanted. Fairy tale creatures.
All right. This one's full.
Take it away!
- Move it along. Come on! Get up!
- Next!
Give me that!
Your flying days are over.
That's 20 pieces of silver
for the witch. Next!
- Get up! Come on!
- Twenty pieces.
Sit down there!
Keep quiet!
This cage is too small.
Please don't turn me in. I'll
never be stubborn again.
I can change. Please!
Give me another chance!
- Oh, shut up.
- Next!
- What have you got?
- This little wooden puppet.
I'm not a puppet.
I'm a real boy.
Five shillings for
the possessed toy.
- Take it away.
- Father, please! Don't let them do this!
- Next. What have you got?
- Help me!
Well, I've got a talking donkey.
Right. Well, that's good for ten
shillings, if you can prove it.
Oh, go ahead, little fella.
Well?
Oh, he's just...
he's just a little nervous.
He's really quite a chatterbox.
Talk, you bone headed dolt...
- That's it. I've heard enough. Guards!
- No, no, he talks!
He does.
I can talk. I love to talk.
I'm the talkingest damn
thing you ever saw.
- Get her out of my sight.
- No, no!
I swear! He can talk!
Hey! I can fly!
- He can fly!
- He can talk!
- That's right, fool!
Now I'm a flying,
talking donkey.
You might have seen a house fly,
maybe even a super fly,
but I bet you ain't never
seen a donkey fly.
Seize him!
After him! He's getting away!
Get him! This way! Turn!
You there. Ogre!
Aye?
By the order of Lord
Farquaad, I am...
authorised to place you
both under arrest...
and transport you to a designated
resettlement facility.
Oh, really?
You and what army?
Can I say something to you?
Listen, you was really, really
something back there. Incredible!
Are you talking to me?
Yes, I was talking to you.
Can I just tell you
that you was great back there?
Those guards!
They thought they was all of that.
Then you showed up, and bam!
They was tripping over themselves
like babes in the woods.
That really made me
feel good to see that.
- Oh, that's great. Really.
- Man, it's good to be free.
Now, why don't you go celebrate your
freedom with your own friends? Hmm?
But I don't have any friends.
And I'm not going out
there by myself.
Hey, wait a minute! I got a great idea!
I'll stick with you.
You're a mean, green,
fighting machine.
Together we'll scare the spit
out of anybody that crosses us.
Oh, wow! That was
really scary.
If you don't mind me saying,
if that don't work,
your breath certainly
will get the job done,
'cause you definitely need some Tic Tacs
or something, 'cause your breath stinks!
You almost burned the
hair outta my nose,
just like the time...
Then I ate some rotten berries. I had
strong gases eking out of my butt that day.
Why are you following me?
I'll tell you why.
'Cause I'm all alone
There's no one here beside me